standupdeskstore.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Stand Up Desk Store | Stand Up Desk Store

LAST UPDATED: February 4, 2019

Stand Up Desk Store, a division of EBSCO Industries, Inc. (“SUDS” or “we”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this Privacy Policy.

SUDS wants you to have a positive experience at the websites we operate. We want you to know that we respect the privacy and security of our users. Our goal is to provide you with an experience that delivers the information, resources and services that are helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, we may collect information from you. We discuss our information collection practices below. This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy principles We follow, in accordance with our operations.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy practices in effect at SUDS’s website (the “Website”) and for information collected through the purchase of our products. If you do not agree to these terms, do not access this Website.

For any questions on this Privacy Policy or our data practices, or to send in a data subject access request, you can contact us using one of the following methods:

### What Information Is Collected and How is it Used?

#### A.    What Information Do We Collect?

**1\. Personal Information:** information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual, including: name, title, date of birth, unique identifier (e.g., account number), company name, job function, expertise, postal address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, geolocation and IP address. If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with our Services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**2\. Non-Personal Information:   **information that does not directly reveal your identity or does not directly relate to an identifiable individual. This might include a unique identifier (unconnected to your username or IP address) and related analytics and usage information that we use to track usage of our Website, track trends in our Website, administer the Website, and improve our users’ experience.

#### B.   How Do We Collect the Information?

We will only collect and use Personal Information when a user voluntarily provides it to us, with the exception of your geolocation and IP address which may be automatically captured when you use our Website. In order to use some portions of our Website, a user must first complete a registration form or provide an e-mail address that will require disclosure of Personal Information. Such disclosure is strictly voluntary. In order to contact us by e-mail, however, you must provide an e-mail address.

We automatically collect non-Personal Information, including web server log files, generated from your use of our Website.  We use this non-Personal Information in the aggregate.  We do not combine these types of non-Personal Information with Personal Information. We may also share aggregated demographic information with our business partners, sponsors, advertisers, and companies that control, are controlled by, or are under common control with SUDS.

_**Cookies**_ :  We may place a "cookie" or other tracking or information gathering device used in the industry in the browser files of a user's computer. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.  We use cookies to collect information about your use of our Website, which enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Website.  We also use cookies from third parties for marketing purposes (such as interest-based online advertising) that allow us to display SUDS promotional material to you on other sites you visit across the internet partners based on your visit to our Website.  Third party cookies are covered by the third party’s privacy policy.

Users can set their browsers or third party software to reject cookies. If a user rejects the cookie, the user may be unable to use portions of our Website. Some of the third-party websites We provide links to also may use cookies. We have no control over these linked Website or access to or control over cookies or other technology used by linked websites.

The following is a list of the cookies that may be used across the Website:

We use these cookies to collect information about how you interact with our Services and to help us improve them.

**Type**|  **Purpose**  
---|---  
Essential | We use these strictly necessary cookies to provide you with services available through our Services and to use some of its features.  
Preference | We use these cookies to authenticate users and help identify and prevent security risks.SecurityWe use these cookies to authenticate users and help identify and prevent security risks.  
Performance | We use these cookies to collect information about how you interact with our Services and to help us improve them.  
  
We use these strictly necessary cookies to provide you with services available through our Services and to use some of its features.

We use these cookies to remember your settings and preferences.

We use these cookies to authenticate users and help identify and prevent security risks.

Performance We use these cookies to collect information about how you interact with our Services and to help us improve them.

In addition, our Website uses cookies provided by third-parties in order, for example, to improve our performance or Website. Some examples of cookies we use within our Website are as follows:

**Type**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
Advertising Cookie by Criteo

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Criteo Corp. collects non-Personal Information that helps us serve relevant ads.  The Criteo Corp.’s privacy policy can be viewed [here](http://www.criteo.com/privacy/).  
  
Analytics Cookie by Addthis

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Oracle Corporation that collects non-Personal Information on user shares of product pages.  The Addthis privacy policy (including information on opting out) can be viewed [here](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy).  
  
Analytics Cookie by Google Analytics

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects aggregate statistical data about how visitors use the Website (i.e., what pages users visit, how long they are on the Website, how they got there and what they click on) so that we can improve the user experience and serve up the content our visitors find most useful.  They do not collect or store Personal Information.

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its analytics service at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).   
Google also offers a tool that allows you to opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites and can be found [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).   
  
Preference/Advertising Cookie by Google

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects data about your preferences and helps customize user ads, but does not personally or directly identify you.   This information may be used in combination with the data collected through the other cookies listed above. 

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its advertising features at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You can also opt out with [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCjR4sMQxSJOzB_v8TNsRdxQm9IOWavuDzrTGX3ANa8kqL6ITAuvJTz80Gcsh_l-z6OoMveMxAUAhfjoO1OxDTVkXfwPgey3tRsdJsgMeZ6oDRf0Wb8&hl=en) or the [NAI’s consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).  
  
DoubleClick by Google (Ad Platform)

| 

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects data about your activities on the Websites and other websites to provide you targeted advertising, but does not personally or directly identify you.   This information may be used in combination with the data collected through the other cookies listed above. 

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its advertising features at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You can also opt out with [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCjR4sMQxSJOzB_v8TNsRdxQm9IOWavuDzrTGX3ANa8kqL6ITAuvJTz80Gcsh_l-z6OoMveMxAUAhfjoO1OxDTVkXfwPgey3tRsdJsgMeZ6oDRf0Wb8&hl=en) or the [NAI’s consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).  
  
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE by Youtube

| 

Sometimes We use YouTube to embed a selection of videos on our website. The embedded videos do not set cookies themselves and can be played with no cookies set. However, if the ‘Share’ button is clicked YouTube will set these two cookies. The VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE cookie attempts to estimate your bandwidth and the use_hitbox cookie increments the ‘views’ counter on the YouTube video. These cookies don’t gather information that identifies a user  
  
YSC by Youtube

| 

This cookie is set by the YouTube video service on pages with embedded YouTube video.  This is a session cookie that is deleted when your browser is closed.  
  
Advertising Cookie by Criteo

A third-party cookie provided by Criteo Corp. collects non-Personal Information that helps us serve relevant ads.  The Criteo Corp.’s privacy policy can be viewed [here](http://www.criteo.com/privacy/).

Analytics Cookie by Addthis

A third-party cookie provided by Oracle Corporation that collects non-Personal Information on user shares of product pages.  The Addthis privacy policy (including information on opting out) can be viewed [here](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy).

Analytics Cookie by Google Analytics

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects aggregate statistical data about how visitors use the Website (i.e., what pages users visit, how long they are on the Website, how they got there and what they click on) so that we can improve the user experience and serve up the content our visitors find most useful.  They do not collect or store Personal Information.

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its analytics service at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

Google also offers a tool that allows you to opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites and can be found [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

Preference/Advertising Cookie by Google

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects data about your preferences and helps customize user ads, but does not personally or directly identify you.   This information may be used in combination with the data collected through the other cookies listed above.

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its advertising features at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You can also opt out with [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCjR4sMQxSJOzB_v8TNsRdxQm9IOWavuDzrTGX3ANa8kqL6ITAuvJTz80Gcsh_l-z6OoMveMxAUAhfjoO1OxDTVkXfwPgey3tRsdJsgMeZ6oDRf0Wb8&hl=en) or the [NAI’s consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).

DoubleClick by Google (Ad Platform)

A third-party cookie provided by Google, Inc. that collects data about your activities on the Websites and other websites to provide you targeted advertising, but does not personally or directly identify you.   This information may be used in combination with the data collected through the other cookies listed above. 

You can find out more about Google’s privacy policy concerning its advertising features at [Google privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

You can opt-out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites [here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). You can also opt out with [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCjR4sMQxSJOzB_v8TNsRdxQm9IOWavuDzrTGX3ANa8kqL6ITAuvJTz80Gcsh_l-z6OoMveMxAUAhfjoO1OxDTVkXfwPgey3tRsdJsgMeZ6oDRf0Wb8&hl=en) or the [NAI’s consumer opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed).

VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE by Youtube

Sometimes We use YouTube to embed a selection of videos on our website. The embedded videos do not set cookies themselves and can be played with no cookies set. However, if the ‘Share’ button is clicked YouTube will set these two cookies. The VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE cookie attempts to estimate your bandwidth and the use_hitbox cookie increments the ‘views’ counter on the YouTube video. These cookies don’t gather information that identifies a user

This cookie is set by the YouTube video service on pages with embedded YouTube video.  This is a session cookie that is deleted when your browser is closed.

SUDS’s Website may use social media features, such as the Facebook ‘like’ button (“Social Media Features”). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on our Website to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party Social Media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features.

_**Web Beacons**_ : SUDS uses web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about customers’ and visitors’ usage of our Website and interaction with emails from SUDS. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular website tied to the web beacon, and a description of a website tied to the web beacon. As with cookies, you can use your browser or app settings to control web beacons.

#### C.   How Do We Use the Information?

We will use the Personal Information we collect for limited internal purposes that may include, but are not limited to, processing your transactions, establishing the identity of account holders, customer service, warranty services, and providing you with information concerning our services. We will retain this information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We also may use that Personal Information to improve and customize our content.

We may use the Personal Information and non-Personal Information we collect by sharing it with third party agents, vendors, contractors, partners, or content providers of SUDS (collectively, "Contractors") for purposes of managing purchases of our products and services, servicing our systems, and obtaining support services for our businesses. We are not in the business of selling Personal Information to third parties or Contractors, and will share it with Contractors only as we describe in this Privacy Policy. In situations where we provide Personal Information to Contractors, we ensure access is granted to the Contractors only upon the condition that the Personal Information is kept confidential and is used only for carrying out the services these Contractors are performing for SUDS. As part of making that determination whether we will provide Personal Information to Contractors, we will obtain assurances that they will appropriately safeguard Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

We may share your usage data related to our Services with our affiliates for purposes of providing or improving our Services. We will not disclose any information about your usage data related to our Services to unaffiliated third-parties, except as necessary to enhance the product experience, service the legal agreement between us and your employer or affiliated institution under which you are provided access to our Services, to enforce the terms of use, to meet our contractual obligations to report aggregated usage data to content providers, or as required by law.

We also reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information if we are required to do so by law, or in the good faith belief that disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect or advance the rights, property, safety, or well-being of our company, our employees, customers, or the public.

We will not use your personal data for automated-decision making.

In the unlikely event that all or substantially all of SUDS’s assets are acquired, customer information, which may include Personal Information, may be one of the transferred assets unless restricted by applicable local law.

#### D.   What is our legal basis for collecting and using your Personal Information? (EEA Only)

Our legal basis for collecting and using the Personal Information described above will depend on the Personal Information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect Personal Information from you only (i) where we need the Personal Information to perform a contract with you or your organization, (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms, or (iii) where we have your consent to do so. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect Personal Information from you or may otherwise need the Personal Information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.

If we ask you to provide Personal Information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with your institution, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your Personal Information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible impact if you do not provide your Personal Information).

Similarly, if we collect and use your Personal Information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your Personal Information, please contact us using the contact information provided above.

#### E.   How Do We Secure Personal Information?

SUDS has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to ensure that Personal Information we have collected or will collect in the future is secure. For example, we have limited the number of people who have access to the Personal Information, by electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. As a reminder, SUDS provides links to third-party websites. These websites may not have the same privacy policies as SUDS. We take reasonable care in recommending these websites but we are not responsible for their content or privacy policies. We urge users to read the privacy statement of a third-party website when leaving our Website and linking to a third-party website.

We always use industry-standard technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you under this Privacy Policy.

#### F.  How Can I Access, Correct, Amend or Remove Information About Me, etc.?

We want to assure you that you have access to your Personal Information that we collect and store. Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. You may contact us either in writing or by e-mail at the contact information stated above to exercise the following rights:

  * Access your data to check and review them
  * Have a copy of your Personal Information
  * Demand that We supplement, correct or delete your Personal Information; or cease or restrict the collection, processing, use or disclosure of your Personal Information; the right of rectification will comprise the right to have incomplete Personal Information completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement
  * Object to the processing of your Personal Information
  * Receive your Personal Information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have it transmitted to another controller; provided that the processing is based on your respective consent or to execute a contractual relationship or a relationship prior to entering into contract with you; and
  * Withdraw your consent where the Personal Information we collect from you is based on your consent.

We will respond to your request within thirty (30) days of receipt.

If you have granted consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time with future effect. Please address your withdrawal by contacting us in writing or by email at the contact information stated above.

If you are located in the EU, after May 25, 2018, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in relation to the processing of your Personal Information.

#### G.    What Choices Do I Have?

We understand that you may not want to allow our disclosure of your Personal Information to our Contractors, or to let us use that information for purposes that you believe may be incompatible with the purpose for which it originally was collected (as permitted by this Privacy Policy) or that you later may authorize. Therefore, you may contact us to inform us that you do not want to permit these uses of your Personal Information. To do so, please contact us by mail or email at the address or email address provided above.

It is important to us that the Personal Information we collect is appropriate and relevant to the purposes for which we intend to use it. We will use Personal Information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the person providing the information. SUDS will take reasonable steps to ensure that Personal Information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current.

You may sign-up to receive email newsletters or other marketing materials from us. If you would like to discontinue receiving this information, you may immediately update your email preferences free of cost by using the “Unsubscribe” link found in emails we send to you or at your account settings on our website or by contacting us at [privacy@ebsco.com.](mailto:privacy@ebsco.com)

#### H.     Collection and Use of Information from Children

Our Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any Personal Information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 16, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us using the information listed above.

#### I.     How Long Do We Retain This Information?

We retain Personal Information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business interest or other legal need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements).

When we have no further legitimate business interest or legal need to process your Personal Information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your Personal Information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

#### J.     What Are My Rights?

Upon request, SUDS will tell you if we process any of your Personal Information. Depending on your country of residency, you may have legal rights with respect to your Personal Information. As such, if you would like to manage, change, limit, or delete your Personal Information, you can do so via the account settings or by contacting us using the information provided above. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

If we process your Personal Information based on our legitimate interests, you can object to this processing in certain circumstances. In such cases, we will cease processing your Personal Information unless we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing or where it is needed for compliance and/or legal reasons. Where we use your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, you can always object or opt out by using the unsubscribe link in such communications or by contacting SUDS using the above contact information.

### EU- U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield

EBSCO Industries, Inc. and its subsidiaries EBSCO International, Inc., EBSCO Publishing, Inc. dba EBSCO Information Services, DynaMed, LLC, Plastic Research and Development Corporation dba PRADCO Outdoor Brands, Summit Treestands, LLC, and Yankee Book Peddler, Inc. dba GOBI Library Solutions from EBSCO (collectively, the “EBSCO Covered Entities”) comply with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of Personal Information transferred from the European Union, the European Economic Area (EEA) or Switzerland to the United States. The EBSCO Covered Entities have certified to the Department of Commerce that they adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at [privacy@ebsco.com](mailto:privacy@ebsco.com).

This Privacy Policy describes the types of Personal Information we collect, the types of third parties to which we disclose this information, and the purposes for which we do so. Residents of the EU and Switzerland have the right to access the Personal Information that the EBSCO Covered Entities maintain, and in some cases, may have the right to correct or amend Personal Information that is inaccurate or has been processed in violation of the Privacy Shield Principles, to the extent allowed by law. To exercise this right, contact us at [privacy@ebsco.com](mailto:privacy@ebsco.com).

The EBSCO Covered Entities remain liable if they transfer Personal Information to third parties who process this Personal Information in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles.

With respect to Personal Information received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, the EBSCO Industries, Inc.isCovered Entities are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.  In certain situations, the EBSCO Industries, Inc.Covered Entities may be required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles,  the EBSCO Covered Entities commit to resolve complaints about their collection or use of your personal information.  EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints may contact SUDS by mail at 5724 Highway 280 E, Birmingham, AL 35242 USA, Attn: Data Privacy Officer or by email at [privacy@ebsco.com](mailto:privacy@ebsco.com).  The EBSCO Covered Entities have further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the U.S.  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website [<https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>], you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.  

### Questions

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices, please send us an e-mail or write to us at the addresses found at that page or listed above.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that We have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We will notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy by posting an updated policy on this page. You agree that continued use of the Website is an acknowledgment and consent to any terms contained in this Privacy Policy, current at the time of use. If We make any material changes We will notify you by means of a notice on this Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Miscellaneous

_**Do Not Track Signals**_ : SUDS does not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include ‘do not track’ instructions.
